KYLE WAGNER

MARKETER | DESIGNER | DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

Marketing manager and digital designer with over four years of professional experience in Southeast Asia. Creative team player with the ability to work cross-culturally with international clients under tight deadlines. Actively learning front-end web development and UI design.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

12/2017 - Current Marketing Manager

Focus Asia Group

Implemented a complete rebranding of our luxury subbrand, Refine Asia, including sales collaterals and a handcoded website. Planned and executed a successful email marketing campaign and a social media strategy.

09/2018 - Current Web Developer, Designer

TYPE-C

Created and designed two microsite pages using Materialize CSS for a marketing campaign aimed at the Singaporean market. Designed and coded three websites using CMS for audio and video production companies.

07/2016 - 04/2019 **Project Coordinator**

GIZ (German Society for International Cooperation)

Developed layout and panel prints for ITB Asia in Singapore for 2 years. Assisted in the development of a booth in Paksé, Laos. Designed a parade banner for *Khiaw*, a sustainability project in Luang Prabang. Created presentations and posters for investors to follow UNESCO regulations.

09/2014 - 09/2017 **Marketing Coordinator**

Tiger Trail Travel

Redesigned entire visual communication platform including print-based advertisements, tour catalogues, logos, and business cards. Developed two responsive websites on Wordpress: Fairtrek.org & Biking-Laos.com.

SKILLS & EXPERTISE

Photoshop
Illustrator
InDesign
Sketch
Adobe XD
Zeplin
HTML/CSS
Javascript

EDUCATION

2015 - 2017 **MA Geography** York University, Toronto, CA

2012 - 2014 **BA International Studies** (Honors) DePaul University, Chicago, USA

SOCIAL

in Linkedin.com/in/kyledwagner

★ t.me/kdwagner

O Instagram.com/kyledwagner

\$\infty\$ +66 80 362 0972